Music
Thank you for watching!
Good evening everyone, this is Takashiya.
We're in the middle of rehearsal for "Super Express" right now.
Well, February 14th has already passed.
It's been a while since we've all had a chance to perform solo.
So I made some Valentine's Day gifts for them.
Here are 8 pieces.
I made truffle chocolates yesterday.
I'm going to give them to everyone at the rehearsal.
Actually, I had a chance to give them only to the staff members and other members that I can see.
I had a chance to give them only to the staff members and other members whom I could meet.
But I haven't given it to all of them yet.
We're all tired from rehearsals, so we're going to give you a supply for the time being.
You know, the kind where the lights go out when you move around.
That's why
I would like to give these chocolates as a gift.
I made one like this.
~~
I call it 315 Api Valentine's Day
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Truffle place of such a feeling ah ah ah ah
Let's go while the book is a truffle place of feelings reflect in half congratulations on the contrary Yeah
Let's go while the book reflects on the contrary with a half
Happy Valentine's Day!
I did it!
A little late.
A little late, but a lot late.
It's not easy to see each other
It's been a while since we've seen each other.
I'm going to eat truffle chocolate.
When did you do that?
Yum!
It's so good!
Wow!
Let's see...
February 23rd. February 23.
Don't tell me to stop.
Oh, it's so cute!
What's this?
Truffle chocolate!
The powder is falling apart!
Oh, it's already fine.
It's the one that's open.
I just zipped it up. It's fine.
Oh, really? I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't have that kind of skill set.
The open one.
I don't have that kind of factory tech.
You're so good.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
That's how I feel.
Oh, my God.
Look at this.
Wow.
Can I just have a big bite of this or something?
Just a bite or something?
Just a little nibble.
Let it melt on your tongue a little bit.
Let it permeate your body.
And if you can, hold the brandy in one hand.
Oh, I see.
I rubbed the whole thing.
Yum.
Chunks of it.
I can't eat you.
This is so good.
This is mine.
I'm gonna eat this so much.
Hey, I want some.
I ain't giving it to you.
It's mine. It's mine.
I think Mr. Takashio is really pissed off.
I think he's really pissed off.
He's really pissed off.
I couldn't make it even if I wanted to.
Can you make this again tomorrow?
I'll make it tomorrow.
And make it early.
I'll batish it.
Batish.
You can stop calling me "batish" if you want.
Even if you go that far, put a picture on it.
LOL!
No problem!
I'm trying to say it exactly as I want to say it.
We've got, uh, Tadashi and Yuki downstairs.
Tadashi and Yuki are downstairs too.
I'll talk to the other members.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it again for the rest of the members.
That's it.
Okay.
Yum.
Happy valentine's time, everyone!
Happy Valentine's Day!
It's so good!
I only like truffles and raw chocolate.
That's good.
It's good again!
Thanks for watching!
Great!
Can you please confirm?
I can't.
I can't! Yum!
Yum!
Yes, sir.
It's monosegalley!
Wow, yum!
Same type!
Oh, this one...
It's zipped, so it's okay.
That's what I'm talking about.
Looks fine.
Yeah, I don't have that kind of skill set.
Yum!
Is it good?
Oh, it's amazing.
It's some kind of coating, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How many enzymes does it have? Like, how many enzymes?
That's amazing.
That's genius.
I feel like I'm eating a big piece of chocolate.
Oh, my God.
Thank you so much!
It's so good.
Thank you so much.
Great job!
Please come again next year
What did Takashi give you?
I received sweets
Tomorrow
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day
Valentine's Day tradition
Second time
the second time
I don't know...
When I got it last year...
I was like, "Oh, thank you."
I don't know what it was, it was a shock.I don't know what it was, but it was a shock.
It's been bad this year.
I was like, "Oh, really?" Right now.
Not at all.
For real? But...
Things have changed. Relationships have changed.
Don't do this, dude.
Ha-ha-ha.
Exasperating.
Ha-ha-ha
Eggy
Takashi's gone.
I'll eat after I get here.
I'll eat it after I get here.
Just the smell alone is delicious.
Ha-ha-ha!